wishberg.com 2014-06-29

# Wishberg / Privacy

This Privacy Policy mentions the privacy practices we follow on Wishberg and the way data is collected and used by us. We refer to Wishberg.com and websites & webpages that are operated under Wishberg together as the "sites" in this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing the services provided by Wishberg you agree to the collection and use of your data by Wishberg for provisioning you the product and service experience on our sites.

### Information Collection and Use

**Account Setup**   
When you set up an account with us, in the process you will provide us your details including the email address and set a password to your account. We may use your email address to send you notifications about your account, information relevant to your account & promotional emails.

**Personal Information** Wishberg respects your privacy and the personal information that you may disclose to us while registering and when you try to avail our services. Because of nature of our product & services, some information might be available on your public profile. Personal information that may be identifiable which includes your full name, email address, contact details, location or telephone numbers shall not be disclosed to any third party without your permission.

**Location Information**   
Some information shared and available on our sites might be very specific to your location. It will be possible for you to define the same and change the location from your account settings.

**Social Networks**   
We allow you to create and link your Wishberg account with social networking sites such as Facebook and Twitter. When you allow us to add our application with your permission, we may receive information about you which includes your name, picture, email address, gender, date of birth, your profile id, your friends profile ids and other information that is made available through their APIs. This information may be used to provision you our services.

**Third Party Services**   
We allow you to integrate with third party services through our sites which include Facebook, Twitter, Gmail and others. Services maybe added or removed from time to time. Our sites will comply and integrate with them through authentication requirements and the API preferences. Some features on our sites will be able to access your details from such services post your authentication. This will include personal data and also information about who you are connected with through those other services. This information will be used to enhance and personalize your experience on our sites. Few features will also enable you to push back notifications to such third party services. We may also use such information and communicate with you about notifications, promotional messages and other communication from time to time. We may share your information with the third party services. The third party's use of that information may be subject to its own restrictions. We will have no control on the third party's intended uses or security.

**Mobile Services**   
We allow you to share details about your mobile contact number with us during the registration. This information may be used to communicate back to you notifications about our services or promotional messages through mobile messaging channels like SMS, WAP, GPRS, GPS, Applications, and so on. If you user our mobile applications, you may also provide us information on your location. We may use this information to personalize experience for you on our product. This information may be used to also display promotional information or advertisements which may or may not be based on your location. We may also use this information to understand your mobile application usage for our application while your try to access our services through such devices. If you are a smart phone user, we may also store any unique reference id that the device may have against your account. Such information will be used to improve usage of our service and provide you a better user experience. Information gathered on any mobile device will be through your mobile carrier who may also have access to same. You will have to contact your mobile carrier to understand their privacy policies.

**Cookies**   
A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services. Our sites may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to improve our Services. A session cookie enables certain features of the service and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the service. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the service. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

**Log Data**   
Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Services. This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any links on which you click. Other actions, such as interactions with advertisements, may also be included in Log Data. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use Log Data to monitor the use of the Service and of our Service.

**Analytics Services**   
Wishberg uses third party analytics services like Google Analytics & others to help understand use of our Service. Such services collect information sent by your browser as page accessed, cookies and your IP address. These services are governed by policies adopted by respective companies.

**Customer Care & Feedback **   
We may also use information provided by you through your interactions with us on email, phone or feedback forms for improvement of our products, services and offerings. The information may be collected using different channels for gathering feedback on Wishberg.

**Contests & Promotions **   
Wishberg may offer users chance to participate in contests & promotions. Any information submitted in such activities will be in accordance with this Privacy and Policy, except as specifically mentioned in the rules for those contests.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

**By Your Consent**   
We may share or disclose your information for business purpose with your consent. Wishberg will do so for business purposes or to provide you services, transactions and benefits provided by our partners, all by your consent through an action initiated by you. This information may be also disclosed when you are using any third party client either developed by us, or any partners to access your Wishberg account.

**Service Providers**   
We may engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services.

**Fraud and Harm**   
We may disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Wishberg rights or property.

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement**   
Wishberg cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process, to protect the property and rights of Wishberg or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

**Business & Ownership Transfers **   
If the ownership of our business changes or our business purpose changes, we may transfer your information to the new owner so that the service can continue to operate. In such a case, your information would remain subject to the change of privacy policy on such event.

**Children**   
Wishberg is not directed to users under age 13. In event you are aware of any child below age of 13 is a user on Wishberg, you are requested to contact us immediately. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. We are become aware or are made aware of such instances; we will terminate such accounts and delete all information stored about these accounts.

### Changing Your Personal Information

**Editing your Profile & Data **   
If you are a registered user of Wishberg, we will provide you options to access & modify your personal information and all other details you have entered about yourself at any point of time. You will have to login and change/update your details.

**Deleting yout Account**  
If you are a registered user of Wishberg, you can login to your account and send request to delete your account on Wishberg. On receiving your request to delete, your account data and your profile information will be deleted within 15 days from this date. In an event if you happen to login to your account in these 15 days, your account deletion request will not be processed.

### Information Security

Wishberg is committed about safeguarding your account and the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We use a combination of firewall barriers, encryption techniques and authentication procedures, among others to secure Wishberg accounts and systems from unauthorized access.

**Account Password**   
When you register with Wishberg we provide you a password to access your account details and protect the information you have shared on Wishberg. We maintain controls to ensure that your passwords are safely stored in encrypted format and are not accessible to anyone. We recommend that you periodically change your password and not share the same with anyone else. Wishberg is not responsible if your account is accessed by anyone other than you based on the information made available by you or by any other means through you. Your password is not even accessible to us.

**Third Parties**   
We may be associated with other organizations, however this policy does not apply to entities that are not managed, owned or controlled by Wishberg. We do not have any control on how information is stored, maintained, displayed and used by such third party services.

If you have any concerns about your account, information security or privacy policy of Wishberg, do get in touch with us. We will work towards answering and resolving your concerns.

### Change of Privacy Policy

We may update this privacy policy from time to time. We will post the changes to this and make the available on our website to make you aware of how we collect and use the information. We hold the right to update this privacy policy at any time, we request you to review the same frequently.

### Contact Information

If you have questions, comments, concerns or feedback regarding this Privacy Policy, do contact us.

### Privacy Policy last updated on 12 April 2012
